Contact

+90 553 503 74 75 (Mobile) gkmngrgn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ gokmengorgen (LinkedIn) gokmengorgen.net (Personal)

Top Skills

Python

Rust

Go

Languages

German (Elementary)

Turkish (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Machine Learning: Regression

Machine Learning Foundations: A

Case Study Approach

Programming Foundations: Algorithms

Creative, Serious and Playful Science of Android Apps

First Look: Rust

Gökmen Görgen

Software Developer

Berlin, Berlin, Germany

Summary

I started programming by contributing to GNU / Linux distributions then I involved in web projects with my Python experience. Later I developed mobile and desktop applications. Now I am interested in Blockchain technologies and Deep Learning.

Experience

Coachfrog AG Lead Software Developer October 2015 - Present

Zürich Area, Switzerland

I took on the role of team leader in a large project with multiple sub-projects. Each project used different technical skills such as Go, Nodejs and Python. The essential component of the project is a calendar and booking system.

Radity
Chief Technical Officer
July 2012 - Present
Istanbul, Turkey

We build tech startups, create digital products, deliver technology projects and put together tailored development teams for startups and grownups. SwissLife, Sherpany, and Coachfrog are some of the companies that we worked.

Markafoni Software Developer October 2011 - June 2012 (9 months) Istanbul, Turkey

I worked in Zizigo ERP project for fixing errors, optimising code base, adding new features, etc. My first task was to send a notification mail to the customers about pending orders in Markafoni ERP. Also, I used Fabric for the deployment commands and Sphinx for writing documentation.

Artistanbul PR Software Developer September 2009 - October 2011 (2 years 2 months)

Istanbul, Turkey

I started to work as a full-stack developer in a startup project named Mappiness (mappiness.com). We deployed all our web projects in Debian GNU / Linux servers. Other projects that I developed actively are ozgurlukicin.com, idata.com.tr, no3.com.tr.

TUBITAK

Software Developer (Intern) August 2009 - October 2009 (3 months)

I developed an application named Puding for installing Pardus from the USB disk. I contributed PiSi package manager and maintained XFCE desktop environment.

Education

Istanbul Arel Universitesi

Master's degree, Management and Organization · (2015 - 2016)

Eskişehir Osmangazi Üniversitesi

Diploma, Economic and Administrative Sciences · (2005 - 2010)

Tekirdağ Anatolian High School

High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2002 - 2005)